Privacy Policy
==============

Last modified: November 1st, 2023

Aidlab, a brand operated under Aidmed Sp. z o.o. (“Aidmed”), is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit the Aidlab website (“Visitors”) and individuals associated with organizations who register to use the Products as defined below (“Customers”). This Privacy Policy (the “Statement”) describes Aidlab's privacy practices in relation to the use of the Aidlab website (www.aidlab.com), other Aidlab websites made available from time to time, and applications and services offered by Aidlab (collectively, the “Products”) as logged-in users, mobile app users (“Users”), and individuals using Products without logging in (“Visitors”). The privacy policy pertaining specifically to products directly associated with Aidmed ("Aidmed Cloud", "Aidmed One", "Aidmed Health") can be found at www.aidmed.ai.

Guiding Principles for Data Processing

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online, as well as to address the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) for our users in the European Union. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. GDPR expands this definition to include data that could indirectly identify a person. GDPR also provides additional rights to EU residents, including the right to access, correct, and request deletion of their personal data. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information and personal data in accordance with our website.

In processing Users' and Visitors' data, we are guided by the following principles:

* Legality, fairness and transparency for the individuals subject to data processing.
* We do not collect more information than we need to provide the services performed by Aidlab.
* We do not use data for purposes other than those mentioned in this Privacy Policy.
* We do not keep data longer than necessary.
* We process data in a way that ensures adequate security, including protection against unlawful or unlawful processing and against accidental loss, destruction or damage.
* We do not disclose data to third parties other than as set out in this Privacy Policy.

Who we are

Aidlab, a brand operated under Aidmed Sp. z o.o. based in Gdańsk, Partyzantów 76 Street, 80-254 Gdańsk, KRS: 0000721886, NIP: 5833290208, REGON: 369656602, e-mail address: contact (at) aidmed.ai ("Aidmed") is the administrator of Users' and Visitors' personal data obtained in connection with Users' or Visitors' use of the Website or services provided through the Website.

What personal information do we collect from the people who visit our websites, use our devices, or interact with our apps?

* Personal Details and Medical Data During Registration

When ordering or registering on our site, app, or device, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number, or other details to facilitate your experience. At this stage, some basic medical data may also be requested to provide you with a personalized service.

* Medical Data Collection from Our Devices

In addition to the information you provide, our devices are designed to collect a range of health and wellness data to give you a comprehensive understanding of your health status. This includes, but is not limited to, Electrocardiogram (EKG) readings, chest movement, blood oxygen saturation (SpO2), motion data (including data from the accelerometer), skin temperature, and more. This data allows us to provide personalized feedback and insights into your health and wellness. Please note that all data collected is strictly used in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

* Sound

While Aidlab version 2.2 and higher includes a built-in microphone, it's important to understand its functionalities. The microphone is capable of recording raw sound and is turned on by default. However, we only gather basic sound features such as sound volume level (in dB) and other sound characteristics that enable us to automatically detect specific sounds like coughing or snoring. Please be assured that the collected sound data cannot be used to reconstruct or recover human speech. If in the future we decide to implement any features that would involve more detailed sound data collection, we will provide advance notice.

* Location Information

To enable full experience when user records their acivities with Aidlab, the application asks for background location permissions. The agreement is optional and can be turned off at any time in the phone and app settings. Background location is used to record and show walks, runs and bike rides on a map, even when screen is turned off or application is in the background.

* Connectivity Data

In order to ensure proper communication and interaction between your device and our products, we collect data related to Bluetooth connections. This data is necessary for enabling discovery services and making our devices detectable. It's important to note that these permissions will be requested, and you have the option to grant or deny them.

* Logs

We collect and maintain logs of various activities within our application and devices. This includes data such as device failures, battery status, activity in our applications, and exercise completion. The collection of this information aids us in improving our services, troubleshooting issues, and providing a personalized experience to our users. Please note that certain types of log data may be periodically deleted as per our data retention policies.

When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or app, connect our devices, place an order, fill out a form, or enter information on our platforms. Information is also collected automatically when using our devices or apps, including health and wellness data, device status data, and activity logs.

How do we use your information?

We use the information we collect from you in various ways. This can be when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, use our apps, or connect our devices. The ways we use this information include:

* To personalize your experience and to deliver content, product offerings, and services that are relevant to you. This includes using your health and wellness data to provide insights and feedback.
* To improve our products and services, using data such as device status and activity logs.
* To better respond to your customer service requests and support needs, using information such as your contact details and device status data.

How do we protect your information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

For your convenience, we use Stripe for processing payments. Stripe securely stores your credit card information, enabling expedited future orders and automating the billing process. We do not directly access or handle your credit card information.

Do we use _cookies_?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

* Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
* Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

Third-party disclosure

Your personal data may be disclosed to third parties, including but not limited to IT service and system providers; which are used to provide the services, to payment processors for our services in order to process and fulfill payments for the services; to service providers necessary to send transactional and product information via email or SMS to the extent that disclosure is necessary to automate, simplify and analyze these processes; third party accounting and bookkeeping services to the extent that disclosure is necessary to provide these services to us; legal advisers and consultants to the extent that disclosure is necessary for the use of their services; and governmental, law enforcement and judicial authorities where required by law. In each case, we will endeavour to ensure that the representatives of the aforementioned authorities request disclosure of the data directly to you. If we are required to disclose your information, we will promptly notify you and provide you with a copy of the request, where the law permits us to do so; to healthcare providers and other entities authorized to access your medical records.

The level of protection for Personal Data outside the European Economic Area (EEA) differs from that provided by European law. For this reason, Aidlab transfers Personal Data outside the EEA only when necessary and with an adequate level of protection.

Aidlab always informs you of its intention to transfer Personal Data outside the EEA at the stage of collection.

We will never sell the Personal Data you provide to us to any third party.

Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

* Users can visit our site anonymously.
* Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
* Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

* On our Privacy Policy Page.
* You can change your personal information by logging in to your account.

How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

Does our site and apps allow third-party behavioral tracking?

Yes.

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

We do not let third-parties, including ad networks or plug-ins collect PII from children under 13.

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

* We will notify users via email, within 1 business day
* We will notify users via in-site notification, within 1 business day

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

How long do we keep your personal data

The personal data of which Aidlab is the controller within the meaning of Article 4(7) GDPR will be processed for the duration of the contract for the provision of services or to lodge an effective objection to the processing in cases where the legal basis for the processing is the legitimate interest of Aidlab. The period of data processing may be extended where the processing is necessary for the establishment and assertion of potential claims or defense against claims, and thereafter only if and to the extent required by law.

Deleting the data

You have the right to delete your data if the following conditions are met:

* You are not in any Team.
    
    You can leave a Team at any time by opening to your Team tab under the [Teams](https://my.aidlab.com/teams) list, and pressing "Leave".
    
* You have a Free plan.
    
    You can cancel your Non-Free plan at any time under the [Plans](https://my.aidlab.com/plans).

You can delete the data by deleting your account. Firstly you need to click on [Settings](https://my.aidlab.com/settings) and then "Delete account". When you delete your account the whole data that you provided before will be automatically deleted. The deletion of data means the anonymization of data allowing for the identification of the User.
